
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "  What is the full form of AWS?",
    answer: "Amazon Web Services",
    options: [
        " Amazon Web Services",
        "Auto Web Services",
        "Applied Web Services",
        "None of these",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Amazon EC2 provides virtual computing environments, known as :",
    answer: "instances",
    options: [
     " messages",
     "chunks",
     "instances",
    "None of the mentioned"
      
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Data stored in __________ domains doesn't require maintenance of a schema.",
    answer: "SimpleDB",
    options: [
      "  SQL Server",
      ".RDS",
       "SimpleDB",
      "Oracle"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following provides access for developers to charge Amazonâ€™s customers for their purchases ?",
    answer: ".FPS",
    options: [
      "FWS",
      ".FPS",
      "FAS",
     "All of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How many EC2 service zones or regions exist ?",
    answer: " 5",
    options: [
     " 2",
"4",
"3",
"5"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the full form of AMI?",
    answer: "Amazon Machine Image",
    options: [
      "Auto Machine Image",
      "Amazon Machine Image",
      "Area Median Income",
      "None of the above"
    ]
},
{
 numb: 7, 
    question: "What are the common types of AMI designs?",
    answer:   "All of the above",
    options:[
      " Hybrid AMI",
      "Fully Baked AMI",
      "Just Enough Baked AMI (JeOS AMI)",
      "All of the above"
    ]
},

{
  numb: 8,
  question: "What are the authentication in AWS?",   
  answer:   " All of the Above",
  options:[
    "Access Key",
"Access Key",
"Access Key/ Session Token",
"All of the Above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is an online backup and storage system?",
    answer: "Amazon Simple Storage System",
    options:[
      "Amazon Simple Queue Service",
      "Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud",
      "Amazon Simple Storage System",
      "Amazon Simple Notification Service"
   
    ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
   question: "Which of the following is not an AWS cloud platform service?",
   answer: "Networking",
   options:[
    "Analytics",
"Networking",
"Mobile Services",
"Internet of Things"
]

},

];